{"text":"function helloWorld() \n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.l\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.lo\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"h\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"he\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hel\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hell\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello \")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello w\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello wo\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello wor\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello worl\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\np\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\npr\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\npri\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprin\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprint\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprint \nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprint h\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprint he\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprint hel\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprint hell\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprint hello\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprint helloWorld\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprint helloWorld()\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprint helloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprint helloWorld();\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprinthelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprinhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprihelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nprhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nphelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"8:04:37 PM [info] Activating VS Code Recorder\n8:06:21 PM [info] Recording started\n","file":"extension-output-MattiaConsiglio.vs-code-recorder-#1-VS Code Recorder","language":"Log"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"## Instructions\n\n1. Install dependencies:\n   ```\n   npm install\n   ```\n\n2. Run tests for all exercises:\n   ```\n   npm test\n   ```\n\n3. Run tests by difficulty level:\n   ```\n   npm run test:easy\n   npm run test:medium\n   npm run test:hard\n   ```\n\n4. Run tests for a specific file:\n   ```\n   npx jest tests/easy/ex1.test.js\n   ```\n\nComplete the functions, run the test, and make sure they all pass. Then zip up the entire folder and send it to me via discord.\n","file":"README.md","language":"markdown"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nc\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nco\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\ncon\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\ncons\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst \n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst \n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst \n=\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst \n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst \n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst \n\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst \n=\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst \n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst +\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst \n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst =\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \"\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \"h\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \"he\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \"hel\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \"hell\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \"hello\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \"hello \"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \"hello w\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \"hello wo\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \"hello wor\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \"hello worl\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst s= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst st= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst str= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst stri= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst strin= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst string= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst stri= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst str= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst st= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst s= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst h= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst he= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hel= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hell= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello= \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello world\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello worl\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello wor\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello wo\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello w\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello \");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hello\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hell\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"hel\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"he\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"h\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.logh\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.loghe\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.loghel\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.loghell\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.loghello\");\n}\nhelloWorld();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.loghello\");\n}\nhelloWorldh();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.loghello\");\n}\nhelloWorldhe();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.loghello\");\n}\nhelloWorldhel();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.loghello\");\n}\nhelloWorldhell();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nconst hello = \"hello world\"\n\n\nfunction helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.loghello\");\n}\nhelloWorldhello();\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"c\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"co\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"con\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"cons\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const \n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const n\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const nu\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num \n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num =\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = \n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 5\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\n\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nc\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nco\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\ncon\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\ncons\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst \n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst n\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst na\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst nam\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name \n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name =\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = \n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = A\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Al\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Ala\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNodeyserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNode;yserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNodyserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNoyserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNyserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyseryserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyseyserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalysyserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyyserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnaserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AlserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AlaserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AlanserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNodeyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNode;yserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNodyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNoyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyseryserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyseyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalysyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnalyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnayserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AnyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = yserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AlyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AlayserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = AlanyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;yserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\ncyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nccyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\ncocyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconscyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconstcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst cyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst scyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst swcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst swicyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switccyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switchcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switch cyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switch =cyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switch = cyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switch = tcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switch = trcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switch = trrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switch = trurcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switch = truercyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switch = true\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switc = true\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switc= true\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switc true\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switctrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst swittrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst switrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst swtrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst strue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst true\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst itrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst intrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst inttrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst intetrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst intertrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interrtrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interrutrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interrupttrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptotrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrcyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\ncyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\ncoyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconsyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconstyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst yserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst ggyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst grgyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst grogyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst grougyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst groupgyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group =gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = []gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,,]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,,]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\n]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nc]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nco]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\ncon]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\ncons]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst n]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst no]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst non]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none  ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none =  ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = n ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = nu ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = nul ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\n ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nc ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nco ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\ncon ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\ncons ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconss ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconsts ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst s ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst Ns ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst Nos ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst Nots ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDs ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDes ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefs ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefis ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefies ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefiees ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefienes ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefies ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefines ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefinees ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefinedes ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined es ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined =es ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = es ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = ues ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = unes ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undes ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undees ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefes ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefies ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefines ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefinees ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptortrue\nrc\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9,\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefinedes ]gyserNodeserNode\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const helloWorld = require('../../exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world');\n\ndescribe('hello world function', () => {\n  test('should log \"Hello World!\" to the console', () => {\n    const consoleSpy = jest.spyOn(console, 'log');\n    helloWorld();\n    expect(consoleSpy).toHaveBeenCalledWith('Hello World!');\n    consoleSpy.mockRestore();\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex1.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const showAllTypes = require('../../exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker');\n\ndescribe('Show All Types function', () => {\n  test('should return an object with all the types', () => {\n    const result = showAllTypes();\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('object');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('array');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('string');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('number');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('boolean');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('null');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('undefined');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('nan');\n    \n    expect(result.object).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.array).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.string).toBe('string');\n    expect(result.number).toBe('number');\n    expect(result.boolean).toBe('boolean');\n    expect(result.null).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.undefined).toBe('undefined');\n    expect(result.nan).toBe('number');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex2.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const screamName = require('../../exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer');\n\ndescribe('Name Screamer function', () => {\n  test('should convert name to uppercase and add exclamation marks', () => {\n    expect(screamName('john')).toBe('JOHN!!!');\n    expect(screamName('Sarah')).toBe('SARAH!!!');\n    expect(screamName('bob smith')).toBe('BOB SMITH!!!');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex6.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\n\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nc\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nco\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\ncon\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\ncons\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst \n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst i\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst id\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk \n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk =\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = \n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = N\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = Na\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nI\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIF\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIF \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nI\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf ()\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (A)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Ar)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Arr)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Arra)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.i)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.is)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray())\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(g))\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(gr))\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(gro))\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(grou))\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\n\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nc\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nco\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\ncon\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\ncons\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconso\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsol\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.l\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.lo\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log ()\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log()\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(a)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(ar)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(arr)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(arra)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(array)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(array)\n\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(array)\ne\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(array)\nel\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(array)\nels\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse i\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(group))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(grou))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(gro))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(gr))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(g))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray())\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(v) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray())\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(va) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray())\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray())\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(d) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray())\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(da) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray())\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(dat) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray())\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray())\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(d))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(da))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(dat))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if ()\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (d)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (da)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (dat)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (data)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (data )\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (data !)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (data !=)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (data != )\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (data != d)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (data != da)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (data != dat)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (data != data)\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (data != data)\n  \n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (data != data)\n\n\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if (data != data)\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelse if(data != data)\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\n \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nc \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nco \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\ncon \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\ncons \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconso \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsol \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole. \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.l \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.lo \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log() \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"\") \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"N\") \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"Na\") \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\") \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\"); \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const showAllTypes = require('../../exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker');\n\ndescribe('Show All Types function', () => {\n  test('should return an object with all the types', () => {\n    const result = showAllTypes();\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('object');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('array');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('string');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('number');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('boolean');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('null');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('undefined');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('nan');\n    \n    expect(result.object).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.array).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.string).toBe('string');\n    expect(result.number).toBe('number');\n    expect(result.boolean).toBe('boolean');\n    expect(result.null).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.undefined).toBe('undefined');\n    expect(result.nan).toBe('number');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex2.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\n\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\ne\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nel\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nels\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelse\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelsei\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif()\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(t)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(ty)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof )\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof d)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof dd)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof dad)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datd)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)c\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)co\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)con\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)cons\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)conso\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)consol\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.l\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.lo\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.log\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.log()\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.log(t)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.log(ty)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.log(typ)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.log(type)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.log(typeo)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.log(typeof)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.log(typeof )\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.log(typeof d)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.log(typeof da)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.log(typeof dat)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeof datad;)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typeo datad;)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(type datad;)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(typ datad;)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(ty datad;)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(t datad;)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif( datad;)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelseif(datad;)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelsei(datad;)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelse(datad;)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelse (datad;)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelse (datad)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelse (data)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelse (dat)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelse (da)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelse (d)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelse ()console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelse )console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\nIf (Array.isArray(data))\nconsole.log(array)\nelseif(data != data)\nconsole.log(\"NaN\");\nelse)console.log(typeof data)\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}r\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}re\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}ree\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}reue\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}reure\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}reurte\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}reue\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}ree\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}rete\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}retue\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}reture\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}returne\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return e\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return ()e\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  \n)e\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n\n)e\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\ne\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \ne\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \ne\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \ns\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nst\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstr\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstri\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstrin\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring:\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: \nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: t\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: ty\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typ\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: type\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof =\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"t\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"th\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"a\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"al\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"ala\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"alan\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"al\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"a\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"A\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Al\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Ala\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Alan\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Alan \"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Alan i\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Alan is\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Alan is \"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Alan is m\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Alan is my\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Alan is my \"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Alan is my n\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Alan is my na\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Alan is my nam\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof = \"Alan is my name\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof  \"Alan is my name\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Alan is my name\"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Alan is my name\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Alan is my nam\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Alan is my na\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Alan is my n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Alan is my \nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Alan is my\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Alan is m\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Alan is \nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Alan is\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Alan i\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Alan \nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Alan\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Ala\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"Al\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"A\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \"\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof \nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeof\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typeo\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: type\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: typ\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: ty\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: t\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring: \nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring:\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstring\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstrin\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstri\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nstr\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \nst\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \ns\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return \n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return ()\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  \n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  s\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  st\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  str\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  stri\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  strin\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string:\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: \n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: t\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: ty\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typ\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: type\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof t\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof th\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof thi\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof this\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof th\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof t\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"A\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Al\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Ala\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Alan\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Alan \"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Alan i\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Alan is\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Alan is \"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Alan is m\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Alan is my\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Alan is my \"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Alan is my n\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Alan is my na\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Alan is my nam\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string: typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  string typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  strin typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  stri typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  str typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  st typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n  s typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof s\"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof st\"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof str\"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof stri\"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof strin\"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof string\"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof string \"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof string:\"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof string: \"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof string\"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof string \"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof string (\"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof string (\"Alan is my name\")\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof string \"Alan is my name\"\n)\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof string \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof strin \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof stri \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof str \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof st \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof s \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof  \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   typeo \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n    typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   s typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   st typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   str typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   stri typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   strin typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   string typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String n typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String na typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String nae typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String nam typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String name typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String name: typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String nam typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String na typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String n typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan is my name\"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan is my name\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan is my nam\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan is my na\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan is my n\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan is my \n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan is my\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan is m\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan is \n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan is\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan i\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan \n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Alan\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Ala\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"Al\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"A\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \"\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof \n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeof\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typeo\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  type\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  typ\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  ty\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  t\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String  \n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String \n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   String\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   Strin\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   Stri\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   Str\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   St\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   S\n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}return (\n   \n);\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const num = 50;\nconst name = Alan;\nconst interruptor = true\nconst group = [1,2,3,6,9]\nconst none = null\nconst NotDefined = undefined\nconst idk = NaN\n\n\n\n\nfunction showAllTypes(data) {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}